She's not the only one listening.
Kimi is a thriller, mystery, crime film directed by Steven Soderbergh.
A tech worker with agoraphobia discovers recorded evidence of a violent
crime but is met with resistance when she tries to report it.
Seeking justice, she must do the thing she fears the most: leave her apartment.
Angela Childs, played by Zoë Kravitz.
Terry Hughes, played by Byron Bowers.
Antonio Rivas, played by Jaime Camil.
Samantha Gerrity, played by Erika Christensen.
Bradley Hasling, played by Derek DelGaudio.
Angela's Mother, played by Robin Givens.
Kimi is a 2022 American thriller film directed by Steven
Soderbergh and written and produced by David Koepp.
The film stars Zoë Kravitz.
It was released on HBO Max on February 10, 2022, to generally positive reviews.
The film explores themes of seattle, washington,
agoraphobia, mental illness, virus, covid-19.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.